al al
al
al
al al
[Music]
[Música]
y
y
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
s
s
ha a
ha a
k k H
k k
al i
al i
Go s
Go
ye
ye
yes
yes
l ha B
l ha
Oh
Oh
ha Oh
ha Oh
B
B
[Music]
[Música]
he
he
ye
ye
[Music]
[Música]
love Oh
love Oh
he
he
[Music]
[Música]
ok
ok
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
ah H
ah H
Oh
Oh
[Music]
[Música]
B Oh
B Oh
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
B
B
Oh w
Oh w
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Ok pe here we Go
Ok pe here we Go
the fin here perform for you if you know the
the fin here perform for you if you know
words you can join to put your hands
the words you can join to put your hands
Together if you W Clap as we Take
Together if you W Clap as we Take
through this monapy
through this monapy
[Music]
[Música]
Donkey
Donkey
Donkey K He's the leader of the bunch
Donkey K He's the leader of the bunch
you know him well He's Finally back to
you know him well He's Finally back to
Kick some ta his Coconut gum can and sps
Kick some ta his Coconut gum can and sps
If he shoots It's G hurt He's bigger
If he shoots It's G hurt He's bigger
faster and stronger to
faster and stronger to
He's the First member of the d
He's the First member of the d
Crew Donkey Kong is
Crew Donkey Kong is
here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
[Music]
[Música]
Why have you all been crying while I was
Por qué habéis estado llorando mientras
taking the dog out What was wrong with you guys Why were you
que sacaba el perro qué os
crying so much while I was taking the
pasaba qu tanto lloro mientras sacado el
dog out I left two tabs open
perro me he dejado abierta dos pestañas
here and you were listening to the music
aquí y estabais escuchando la música
double You were listening to the music
doble estabais escuchando la música
double That's what was going on But
doble eso es lo que estaba pasando Pero
anyway let's see gossip no danian Cat
bueno vamos a ver chismos no danian Cat
joins the comments against
se une a los comentarios contra el
Ari's abdomen Gameplay I mean I love it
abdomen de Ari Gameplay O sea me encanta
because it's not like they don't make
porque ya no es como que no es que hagan
comments against Ari as such but
ya comentarios contra Ari como tal sino
comments against AR's abdomen
comentarios contra el abdomen de AR
Gameplay what do you think of
Gameplay qué os parece
my general mind Javi seven words
mi mente general Javi siete palabras
mondongo I mean
mondongo digo
essence Why are you always
esencia Por qué siempre me estáis
messing with me and touching my dick
vacilando y me estáis tocando la [__]
all [ __ ] day long you want a ban that's what
todo el [__] día queréis baneo eso es lo
you want
que queréis
666 free r
666 free r
666 free
666 free
666 [ __ ] man you guys are always
666 [__] tío que siempre estáis
messing around it seemed like music made by
vacilando parecía música hecha por
marius tiberian face crying loudly I got
marius tiberian cara llorando fuerte me
scared marius Mari to crazy but marius
asusté marius Mari to rayado pero marius
to crazy with niser to niser leave her
to rayado con niser a niser la dejas en
alone okay buddy Let's see I want to see
paz vale colega A ver quiero ver un poco
the members a bit and we continue okay
los miembros y continuamos vale
2946 members man I mean I can't
2946 miembros tío O sea no me puedo
believe we stayed But if
creer que nos hayamos quedado Pero si
yesterday we passed them not much because
ayer los pasamos no sobrado eso porque
every day maybe there are some that are
cada día a lo mejor como hay algunos que
not renewed then others do I mean what
no se renuevan pues otros sí O sea qué
[ __ ] madness no this no
[__] locura no esto
What [ __ ] madness Let's see let's
no Qué putísima locura A ver vamos a
update the bar to see if with this
actualizar la barra a ver si con esto la
people get a little motivated [ __ ] man I [ __ ]
gente se motiva un poco [__] tío me
on 10 the 3000 six words calm down
cago en 10 los 3000 seis palabras serene
man the 3000 members How do they play hard to get
tío los 3000 miembros Cómo se hacen de
eh so that later I get there to
rogar eh para que luego llegue yo allí a
the gentlemen guys they have 3000
la señoreros chavales tienen 3000
members or
miembros o
4000 members the salce day
4000 miembros la salce día cantidad
target amount 4000 eh Because we are already here
objetivo 4000 eh Porque ya estamos aquí
as who says let's see I said  2946
como quien dice a ver he dicho 2946
Leonardo DiCaprio the bail of
Leonardo DiCaprio la fianza de
ra I don't know if I'm going to touch on that subject even though I
ra no sé si voy a tocar ese tema aunque
put it in the title the truth is
lo haya puesto en el título la verdad es
that it gives me a little embarrassment The boy and I
que me da un poco de apuro El muchacho y
don't know if I'm going to touch on it eh It gives me the creeps it gives me the creeps
no sé si lo voy a tocar eh Me da cosa me
and I don't know the truth I don't know it
da cosa y no lo sé la verdad no lo sé me
gives me the creeps it gives me the creeps it gives me
da cosa me da me da puro me da
pure Melvin Thank you very much welcome I
puro Melvin Muchas gracias bienvenido
want you to become a member if today
quiero que os hagáis miembro si hoy
we are going to reach 3000 because I
vamos a llegar a los 3000 porque
understand that we will get there there are not 53 left I understand that we will
entiendo que llegaremos no faltan 53
get there okay but I
entiendo que llegaremos vale pero quiero
want you to do it one by one I mean I don't want me to give away 50
uno o sea no quiero que regalé 50
members or 20 members or five
miembros ni 20 miembros ni cinco
members I want you to do it one by
miembros quiero que lo hagáis de uno en
one because the bar only moves when
uno porque la barra solo se mueve cuando
it's one by one so
es de uno en uno
doing it is please okay I'm
entonces hacerme es faor vale me hace
excited let's see let's see let's see the
ilusión veamos veamos veamos veamos la
pullita that Dan has launched here the
pullita que ha lanzado aquí Dan
coscu thing is the dick never Better
lo de coscu es la [__] nunca Mejor
said but let's see how I deal with that subject without
dicho pero a ver cómo trato ese tema sin
eating a
comerme un
p [ __ ] guys man you have me fed up with
p [__] chavales tío me tenéis hasta los
danian K joins the
[__] danian K se une a los
comments against  the abdomen of Ari
comentarios contra el abdomen de Ari
Game Play controversy piece sun very well
Game Play polémica pedazo sol muy bien
thank you very much does it add up or not
muchas gracias suma o no
add up let's see if if I have
suma a ver si si he
given away if I have given away it doesn't add up dude if
regalado si he regalado no suma
given away it adds up it has to be that
tío si regalado suma tiene que ser que
each one of us becomes a member one by one I'm
cada uno de uno en uno se haga miembro
sorry dude it doesn't add up it doesn't add up it has to
Lo siento tío no suma no suma tiene que
be that those who are not members
ser que los que no sean miembros se
become members one by one whatever he
hagan miembros de uno en uno sea sea
comes to show off and he has given us 20
viene a vacilar y nos ha regalado 20
come on seba dude vasila marked you you
venga va seba tío te ha marcado la
are already the coolest in the class
vasila ya eres el más chulo de la clase
I spent all my money on tinder It's not
me gasté todo mi dinero en tinder No es
my problem to look for yourselves to get into debt
mi problema buscaros la vida endeudar
eh And do what you see
eh Y hacer lo que veáis
okay danian cas joins the comments
vale danian cas se une a los comentarios
against the abdomen of AR Gameplay or in other words
contra el abdomen de AR Gameplay o sea
big controversy between the abdomen of AR
polémica gorda entre el abdomen de AR
Gameplay and danian K who you already know is
Gameplay y danian K que ya sabéis que es
an enemy from the past with whom she has
una enemiga del pasado con la que ha
had many controversies in fact I want to
tenido muchas polémicas de hecho quiero
remind you taking advantage of the fact that danian is coming out I
recordaros Aprovechando que sale danian
always remember that danian
siempre lo recuerdo que danian me
contacted me in his day so that I would
contactó en su día para que yo
organize a debate here that could have
organizara un debate aquí eso pudo haber
existed if Ari Gameplay hadn't
existido si Ari Gameplay no se hubiese
gone to town eh that could have  existed
ido al pueblo eh eso pudo haber existido
eh danian She contacted me to
eh danian Me contactó para que
organize a debate here Between her and
organizara aquí un debate Entre ella y
Ari
Ari
Gameplay and Ari told me something like I
Gameplay y Ari me dijo algo así como yo
don't give her I don't want to give her fame or something
no le doy no quiero darle fama o algo
like that, she's not gaml with her abdomen because it
así no s gaml con su abdomen por porque
turns out that the other day she published a
resulta ser que el otro día publicó una
photo of her abdomen and because it generated
foto de su abdomen y por generó
controversy Well because she has had surgery and that's
controversia Pues porque se ha operado y
it and here are several
ya está y ya está aquí varios
comments
comentarios
cited the operated abdomens look
citados los abdómen operados se ven
shitty but if you look well noes it
[__] pero si se le ve bien noes
looks good No no it
se ve bien
's not because of Ari but as an
No no es porari pero como estudiante de
anatomy student they did a little bit of
anatomía te hicieron un trabajo poco
organic work you could have had a better
orgánico pudiste haber tenido un mejor
result the bruises and the scar from the
resultado los moretones y la cicatriz de
[ __ ] lipo is an alipo what has been done and
zorrona es un alipo lo que se ha hecho y
well basically there commenting on
bueno básicamente ahí comentando sobre
the tomen of no And what happened Well it
la tomen de no Y qué ha pasado Pues
turns out that Dani has published a
resulta ser que Dani ha publicado una
photo today in which abdomen curious
foto hoy en el que abdomen curioso
after a day I love my abdomen
después de un día me encanta mi abdomen
of what happened with her publishes that and
de lo que pasó con ella publica eso y
stops says I love my abdomen
parao dice me encanta mi abdomen el de
Leticia Sabatera's horrible Yes it's true
Leticia sabatera horrible Sí es verdad
there are some that look very
hay algunos que se quedan muy
ugly Leticia Sabater who
feos Leticia sabater que
looks like Jul Hogan no with that abdomen no  I know it's
parece jul hogan no con ese abdomen no
very strange a gin diet Yes look in the
sé es muy raro una dieta gin Sí mira al
end there are diets that are very hard very very
final hay dietas que son muy duras muy
hard this time my stomach is hurting me
muy duras yo esta vez me está costando
and this week you will see
la barriga y esta semana verás tú el
this week you will see the nutritionist
esta semana verás tú la nutricionista
when she catches me because this week I have
cuando me coja porque esta semana la
not followed the diet very very very scrupulously I have
dieta no la he seguido muy muy muy arras
eaten junk food a couple of
tabla he comido comida basura un par de
times
veces
you know when the nutritionist is on
sabes cuando es la nutricionista el
Wednesday I mean I am missing nothing from now until
miércoles O sea me falta nada de aquí al
Wednesday I am not going to lose anything this this
miércoles no voy a perder nada este esta
week this week I am not going to have good
semana esta semana no voy a tener buenas
news and that is a bit demotivating but
noticias y eso desmotiva un poco pero
well maybe I will gain muscle mass
bueno a lo mejor gano gano masa muscular
that I am always gaining
que eso siempre estoy ganando
the whole fortnight that I
tod la quincena que
go There is never a lack of expert throwing
voy Nunca falta el experto tirando
[ __ ] XD Who are you referring to tun tun the
[__] XD A quién te refieres tun tun el
expert Ah the [ __ ] expert always
experto Ah el experto [__] siempre
on Twitter an expert always appears on
de Twitter siempre aparece un experto en
Twitter yes
Twitter sí
eh look but with one of the diets that I
eh mira pero con una de las dietas que
did last year which was the one with which I
que hice el año pasado que fue con la
made the video that video I am going to
que hice el vídeo que ese vídeo lo voy a
delete I made like a video of my
borrar hice como un vídeo de mi cambio
physical change but because I committed to
físico pero porque me comprometí con con
the nutritionist but the truth is that I am
la nutricionista pero la verdad es que
going to delete it because that physical change
lo voy a borrar porque ese cambio físico
what I did was stay super thin and it was
lo que hice fue quedarme super delgado y
noticeable on me the six pass
que se me notó el se me notó el six pass
not the six p No but I uploaded it in the
no el six p No pero lo subí en el
main page no I mean it was
principal no O sea fue
like the truth is that diet was very very very very very
como la verdad es que esa dieta era muy
hard very very very
muy muy muy muy dura muy muy muy
strict very
estricta muy
screwed up Oh I don't even have it I would delete it
jodida Ah ni lo tengo lo borraría
yes I would delete it now Javi the
ya sí lo borraría ya Javi se viene
second season of Ari's powerful off is coming it
segunda temporada de off potente de Ari
was in his Prime and billing that
estaba en su Prime y facturando que se
Juan grabs that photo in bed will
agarre Juan esa foto en la cama le
cost him
saldrá
dearly I think Juan I will not care anymore
cara yo creo que Juan le daré un poco
no I don't know the truth I don't know
igual ya no no lo sé la verdad yo no sé
if it will affect him what ario haa no the
si a le afectar lo que haa ario no la
truth I wouldn't know what to tell you in that
verdad No sabría que deciros en ese
sense Dani launches a pullita against dan
sentido Dani lanz pullita contra dan
Wind's friend is part of the
amiga de Wind forma parte del triángulo
chic
de chic
op triangle that they form I don't know for the first one
op que forman no sé por le la primera
that she forms Windy and Ari yesterday uploaded
que forman ella windy y Ari ayer subió
a tweet saying how much she likes
un twet diciendo lo mucho que le gusta
her abdomen when the day before Ari
su abdomen cuando el día anterior Ari
was criticized for his There it is
era criticado por el suyo Ahí está
You know Ari's story with
Ustedes saben la historia de Ari con
Danian there is a lot of love behind it And I think
danian hay mucho lor detrás Y yo creo
that people who have followed controversies for
que la gente que sigue polémicas hace
many years will know that these two do not
muchos años sabrá que estas dos no se
get along at all Not here we have  the
llevan nada bien No aquí tenemos el poz
original post danian c video and that's a whole
original danian c video y eso todo un
video just a video now
video nada más un video ya está ahora
the comments is a post with
bien los comentarios es un post de
11,000 likes 114 comments and here
11,000 likes 114 comentarios y aquí
we have one right above a really shitty
justamente tenemos a uno justo arriba un
abdomen haha there they compare her
abdomen todo [__] jaj ahí la comparan
with ig the one above is melting
con ig la de arriba se está derritiendo
Hahaha in people on Twitter she is really
Jajaja en la gente en Twitter es bien
shitty it's not a complaint at all XD what How
culera para nada es queja XD que Cómo
that in people on Twitter I don't understand I
que en la gente en Twitter no entiendo
understood that reference people people
entendí esa referencia la gente la gente
are getting not a big hint people
está captando no gran indirecta la gente
get operated anyone would say the
capta operado cualquiera diría lo
same always gets good references
mismo siempre saca buenas referencias
this chick live XD the day
esta morra en directa XD el día en que
this woman greets me I become a
esta mujer a mí me salude me vuelvo
Christian
cristiano
qu When did the operation come out Ah no what did
qu Cuándo salió la operación Ah no cuá
the operation come out says one over here
salió la operación dice un por aquí
well without further comments beautiful t such
bueno sin más comentarios hermosa t tal
good comment normal that those above
bueno comentar normal que los de arriba
were more coherent down They are already talking about those
eran más coherentes abajo Ya sonind esas
things no there are no quotes either I [ __ ] myself
cosas no no hay citados tampoco me cagoo
The fact is that yes This was obviously
El caso es que sí Este evidentemente era
a comparison Well what people
una comparación Bueno lo que la gente
are bringing up was a hint let's
está sacando en cara era una indirecta
not go
no yamos
with it because this has been harsh
con elst porque este ha sido duramente
criticized and has received comments of
criticado y ha recibido comentarios de
that style says around here nobody takes me off the
ese estilo dice por aquí nadie me baja
boat unen operated it will always
del barco unen operado siempre se va a
look horrible let's see dan supposedly is
ver horrible a ver el dan supone que es
operated also or how is the thing I don't know
operado también o cómo es la cosa no sé
but danian's well operated is not
pero el de danian pues operado no está
better than him I think Noa Yes well yes and I don't
mejor que el creo yo Noa Sí pues sí y no
know what is due but it's good I am
sé qué se debe pero está bueno Yo soy
those who say that each one has their body
los que dice que cada uno su cuerpo
quear and such no I mean it is exhibited
tiene quear y tal no O sea se exhibe
Well self-esteem but well to each
Pues bien autoestima pero pues a cada
taste to each person's taste well There will be
gusto a gusto de cada persona pues Habrá
people who do not like it like that not marked and
gente que no le guste así no marcado y
such well he says here one how incredible
tal bueno el dice aquí uno qué increíble
that literally all the responses of this
que literal todas las respuestas de esta
photo ar are men now it is I saw it in
foto ar son hombres ahora es lo vi en
another comment But in the end below there were
otro comentario Pero al final más abajo
women like here
habían mujeres como aquí
[Music]
[Música]
criticizing you but imagine investing
criticándote pero imagínate invertir
so much gu in a surgery and it looks like that it does
tanta gu en una cirugía y que se ve así
not look horrible because I have seen worse
tampoco se ve horrible porque vi peores
but it is noticeable that it is not done well well there are
pero sí se nota que no está bien hecho
also women who criticize her
buen también hay mujeres que la critican
eh look at that will make a queen and nothing to
eh mira que hari una reina y nada que
do with her but how ugly is the lipon
ver con ella pero lo feo que es la lipon
and the best surgeon will leave your
y el mejor cirujano les va a dejar lindo
body beautiful I prefer to be fat than to have
el cuerpo Prefiero ser gorda que tener
the  belly like that You don't have to
la panza así Tampoco tampoco hay que
think like that either, obviously No, not being like
pensar así eh evidentemente No no ser
that thin because today, but I think that
así delgada porque hoy pero yo creo que
as long as you're healthy, you're healthy. Well, I don't
mientras estés sano sana Pues bien No
think any, none, but say something while
creo que ninguno ninguno pero di algo
I'm falling asleep, okay, I'll tell you something. Ok, and
que me duermo vale os digo algo Ok y
with this, I'm going to close this exo. Ok, I was
con esto voy a cerrar este exo Ok estaba
putting this
poniendo este
incredible tweet that with so many
tweet increíble que con tanto clip
funables clips of gibel talking [ __ ] about
funables de gibel hablando [__] de
ander And of all the streamers
ander Y de todos los streamers
justifying bullying, making fun of
justificando el bullying burlándose de
autistics, etc., it's incredible that with
autistas etcéteras increíble que con
all this they put him and they
todo esto lo hayan metido a él y al tío
still have Uncle Sur on a blacklist
Sur lo sigan teniendo en una Lista negra
XD an You see, Uncle Sur, lukewarmness is
XD an Ya ves tío Sur la tibieza no sirve
useless You had to be like gibel to
de nada Tenías que ser como gibel para
be able to rub shoulders with the elite on the
poder codear con la élite en el twit
biggest rival tweet of all, you had to
rival más grande de todos tenías que
make CP jokes, justify
hacer chistes de CP justificar el
bullying in schools, defaming
bullying en los Colegios difamar la
lukewarmness was useless to you,
tibieza no te sirvió de
a hug to my partner Uncle
nada un abrazo a mi compañero el tío
Shur and Congratulations on getting in, I
shur y Enhorabuena por haber entrado que
know that for a couple of years now he
sé que que hace un par de años que que
wanted to get in here, that he was excited to
quería entrar aquí que le hacía ilusión
be in a series like this,
estar en una serie como esta
and well, we are with him, we are with him and I hope he has
y pues estamos con él estamos con él y
a lot of luck  and that it lasts at
que tenga mucha suerte y que dure por lo
least that it lasts many days winning is very
menos que dure muchos días ganar es muy
complicated but at least that it lasts
complicado pero por lo menos que dure
that it lasts many days and some clines
que dure muchísimos días y unos clines
for that monkey that was there
para el el macaco ese que estaba ahí
crying that I don't even know who the [ __ ] he is they
llorando que no sé ni quién [__] es
say he had a YouTube channel a
dicen que tenía un canal de YouTube hace
long time ago but that he lost it I don't know why
tiempo pero que lo perdió no sé por qué
but oh well a kiss I'm very happy handsome let's
pero bueno un beso me alegro muchísimo
see
ver
we have
tenemos
news no the one from Cell was the one from Cell it was bite
novedades no el de Cell era el de Cell
no the one from cel it was
no el de cel era
bit I mean come on
bit digo yo vamos
wait the one from Uncle Sur I knew about it a
espérate el de tío Sur lo sabía yo de
few days ago That's why I
Hace unos días Por eso os
told you Let's go that's why I told you that there were no
dije Vamos por eso os dije que que no
betos And I also asked Auron
había betos Y además le pregunté a auron
too and that there are no betos we are not banned anymore what happens is that I
también y que no hay betos no estamos ya
'm banned what happens is that I'm banned
baneado lo que pasa es que estoy baneado
guys that's what
chavales eso es lo que
happens Anyways look I spoke with
pasa De todas maneras ya mira hablé con
ivai yesterday I spoke with well I spoke with
ivai ayer hablé con bueno hablé con
several of those that I think may have
varios de los que yo creo que pueden
eh Wait he sent me
tener eh Espérate que me me ha mandado í
an audio one moment I'm going to
un audio un momento lo voy a
listen to it
escuchar al
everyone raise your
todos levanten sus
hands There's
manos al
no way dude
No hay manera tío
no dude Look they are  several creators
e no tío Mira son varios creadores lo
have tried in some
que han intentado de alguna
way to pull like this a little bit
manera tirar así un poco
of trying to give me a hand talk
de de intentar echarme un capote hablar
to someone or this and that But what's going on man there's
con alguien o tal y cual Pero qué va tío
no
es que no hay
way what Unfair For me everything was
manera qué Injusto Para mí todo fue
connected they haven't been Let's see it's not for
conectado no han sido A ver no está para
me it's already been a series
mí ya está han sido una serie
of it has been What a shame
de ha sido Qué pena
eh What a shame What a shame man it makes me so
eh Qué pena Qué pena tío me da mucha
sorry man
pena hombre
Anica evasion of B it's either because I
Anica evasión de B es o bien porque
appeared in gibel's or sell's Stream
aparecí en el Stream de gibel o de sell
but I think not because in that case they
pero creo que no porque en ese caso los
would have banned them
hubieran baneado a ellos
too or or because they created an account not
también o o porque se crearon cuent no
of Javi oliveira 2 and they were streaming not
de Javi oliveira 2 y estaban streame no
the next day
al día siguiente
m that I can't do anything else man I
m que no puedo hacer otra cosa tío yo a
fought
peleé
and and they have rejected the appeal is that
y y me han rechazado la apelación es que
something else I can't do I
otra cosa no puedo
think that's not
hacer yo creo que es que eso no está
for me eh What a shame eh how good we wouldn't have had it
para mí eh Qué pena eh que bien no lo
eh Javi we read your lips you told him
eh Javi te leímos los labios le dijiste
Hello my biscuit I was anxious
Hola bizcochito mío estaba en ansioso
to hear your sensual voice love I'm
por escuchar tu sensual voz amor estoy
super hot now for your aud shame
super caliente ahora por tu audé pena
What a
Qué
shame What a shame we would have had a good time
pena Qué pena lo hubiéramos pasado bien
man how Unfair I had it  super deserved it would have
tío qué Injusto lo tenía super merecido
been at another time
es que hubiera sido en otro momento
Ah but what are we doing man What are we doing if you
Ah pero qué vamos tío Qué vamos s
had lasted half an hour grandpa Don't get
hubieras durado media hora abuelo No te
depressed Yes of course that's also true
deprimas Sí claro eso también es verdad
if now for whatever reason for the 4th
si ahora por lo que sea para el 4
we are here don't worry that on the first
estamos no os preocupéis que el primer
day I fall georgio a kiss a kiss that's
día caigo georgio un beso un beso que es
true anyway there was no room
verdad de todas maneras no había hueco
eh Anyway there was no room now Eh
eh De todas maneras no había hueco ya Eh
today the last
ya hoy se anuncian los últimos
participants are announced that are confirmed anyway there was no room
participantes que están confirmados de
now [ __ ] I don't hear the I don't hear that man
ya [__] no escucho la no escucho eso
now no no don't think about conspiracies
ahora no no no penséis en conspiraciones
and things like that I mean it's been a series
y cosas de esas o sea han sido una serie
of
de
events happened happened happened live happened
acontecimientos pasó pasó pasó en
live but c9 love Javi F for you A
directo de pero c9 amor Javi F por ti Un
kiss georgio What a shame man Really what a
beso georgio Qué pena tío De verdad qué
shame
pena
I still remember how much fun I had
Todavía me acuerdo lo bien que me lo
watching you in the first squid face
pasé viéndote en los primeros squid cara
crying loud face crying loud
llorando fuerte cara llorando fuerte
face crying loud you realize that
cara llorando fuerte te das cuenta que
you never really lost
tú realmente nunca perdiste
Hahaha Auron's mother asked him not to
Jajaja la madre de auron le pidió que no
let him in no matter what
lo deje entrar da igual lo que Hubiera
Auron's mother would have thought The problem the
pensado la madre de auron El problema la
mother of  auron can't have any
madre de auron no puede tener ningún
power in a ban no
poder en en un baneo no
eh but it's a
eh pero es una
shame It's a shame It's a
pena Es una pena Es una
shame What was r's statement now
pena Cuál fue el comunicado de r ahora
let's see what Ray did but well let's see
vamos a ver lo de Ray pero bueno a ver
we'll cover the gossip that happens No yeah
cubriremos el chisme que ocurra No sí
look on the bright side those days that
miradlo por el lado bueno esos días que
we would have thrown in well we would have been
hubiesemos echado pues hubiéramos estado
full on the skit those days Well I think it
full en los skit esos días Pues creo que
's 4
son 4
hours I think it's 4 hours and And
horas creo que son 4 horas y Y
obviously well that would have been what we
evidentemente pues esa hubiera sido lo
would have
que lo que hubiéramos
done but what a
hecho pero qué
pain what the [ __ ] is that
putada qué [__] es
let's laugh for a while to
eso vamos a reírnos un rato para
cheer ourselves up
animarnos
more I can't make a
más no puedo hacer
family or I mean I told him with the
familia o sea le se lo comenté con los
con The most powerful streamers I
con Los streamers más potentes que
know that are on Twitch and If
conozco de de que están en Twitch y Si
none of them
ninguno de ellos
eh Yes none of them can do anything
eh Si ninguno de ellos puedan hacer nada
It's that on twit they are like very are like very
Es que en twit son como muy son como muy
hermetic
herméticos
dude let's see let's have a
tío a ver vamos a echar unas
laugh we'll talk to Speed I
risas hablaremos con Speed
don't miss Rubius I haven't spoken to Rubius
no me falta Rubius con Rubius no he
but why I mean yes
hablado pero para qué O sea
why doesn't he enter the game because he's
qué no entra al juego porque está
banned period No no Let's see the only
baneado punto No no A ver el único
reason why he didn't enter is because of the
motivo por el que no entro es por el
ban  eh stop with the conspiracies and
baneo eh dejaro de conspiraciones y
stuff like that, no, it's not like
cosas por el estilo que no que no es por
that, you missed it Call my
ahí te faltó Llamar a mis
baseballs Let's see what the [ __ ] he
beis A ver vamos a ver qué [__] me ha
sent me Ale
mandado Ale
what the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] Dallas vs.
qué [__] es esta [__] Dallas contra
Javiro 2018 in Dragon Ball version I
javiro 2018 en versión Dragon Ball se me
got the idea because just like Vegeta
ocurrió la idea porque igual que Vegeta
started out as a villain Ah look, it's nice
inició como Villano Ah mira está bonito
Eh but something happens every year But
Eh pero todos los años pasa algo Pero
anik let's see what happened it happened
anik a ver lo que ha pasado pasó en
live, I mean, we sacrificed ourselves to
directo o sea nos hemos sacrificado por
win a debate
por ganar un debate
time will prove the chat right you'll
el tiempo le dará la razón al chat ya
see No, I don't think it was a
verán No yo no lo creo que haya sido una
conspiracy or anything like that, I mean it happened it happened
conspiración ni nada por el estilo o sea
live while I was here yes it
pasó pasó en directo estando aquí sí que
's true that the second
es verdad que el segundo
bam the second Bang is very gratuitous
bam el segundo Bang es muy gratuito
man I mean the first Bang for me wasn't either either
tío o sea el primer Bang para mí tampoco
The weird thing is the permanent one but the
era Lo raro es el permanente pero el de
7 day one isn't either eh the 7 day one isn't either
7 días tampoco eh el de 7 días tampoco
eh the 7 day one from
eh el el de 7 días por la foto de
Liy's photo you couldn't see
liy tampoco se veía
anything either that's
nada
starting from the base that the
eso es que partiendo desde la base que
first one but well still the
el que el primero pero bueno todavía el
first one I said okay come on 7 days I'll eat it
primero dije yo bueno venga 7 días me lo
But when I saw the two of them  days
como Pero cuando me vi a los dos días
that the indefinite one appeared, say this,
que apareció el indefinido ese di esto
what the [ __ ] is it?
qué [__]
But
es Pero
well, let's see about
bueno vamos a ver lo de
r, the same thing was seen as in the
r se veía lo mismo que en la categoría
Hot t category, nothing was seen, they were censored photos,
Hot t no se veía nada eran fotos
eh, if they ban you, you should have been for threats, but
eh si te banean debías por amenazas pero
for the photo, for threats. Not
por la foto por amenazas
even because you tell a guy if you
Tampoco porque tú le digas a un tío si
mention my children again, I'll
vuelves a mencionar a mis hijos te vuelo
jinx you. Well, yes, a little, yes, a little,
las gafada Bueno sí un poco sí un poco
but it depends, no, it depends, let's see. They
sí pero depende no depende a ver Tampoco
were not very, very aggressive threats either
tampoco fueron unas amenazas muy muy
[Laughter]
[Risas]
eh, justified threat exactly,
eh amenaza justificada exactamente
German. Hey, but they have shut up
German Oye pero se han callado
[Music]
[Música]
talking about r, okay, by the way, it
hablando de lo de r vale que por cierto
seems like gold to me that whoever sues
oro me parece oro que el que demande a
ra is called
ra se llame
sereno, I mean, I think that I think what we are dealing with is
sereno o sea yo creo que yo creo que lo
taking a complaint. I think what
que estamos toma denuncia yo creo que lo
we are experiencing here is
que estamos viviendo aquí
that they are
es son
actors, they are not preparing us, they
actores no nos están preparando todos
are all actors, man, nothing more. eh, the ironies
son actores tío sin más eh las ironías
of life
de la vida
are not actors, man, there is no
no son actores tío no hay
more, it can't be any other
más es que no puede ser de otro de otra
way, man, you paid for this whole show, it's that
forma tío tú pagaste todo este show es
the geeks that
que los frikis que se nos
approach us, the geeks that
acercan los frikis que me
attack me are
atacan son
always, I think they are actors that
siempre yo creo que son actores que me
turn me on  here to create content
ponen aquí para crear contenido
dude it's
tío es
brutal calm dude there were names to
brutal sereno tío había nombres para
give him well he's calm [ __ ]
ponerle pues es sereno [__]
wait ask Frank to talk to
espérate Pídele a Frank que le hable a
elk so that he hits you and tells the ceo of
elk para que azos y él le diga al ceo de
T to take away your bancara smiling with his
T que te quite el bancara sonriendo con
eyes closed
los ojos cerrados
Hahahaha
Jajajaja
well nothing happens family let's see in the
bueno no pasa nada familia a ver al
end the reason let's see what RAE has said
final el motivo vamos a ver qué ha dicho
about the subject because RAE has said
RAE sobre el tema porque RAE ha dicho
that everything is a lie okay the police
que todo es mentira vale que la policía
lie that the justice of Miami lies
miente que la justicia de Miami miente
that he hasn't done anything there he is calm
que él no ha hecho nada ahí está sereno
we found him dear delox
lo encontramos querido delox
precisely that's where I was going it calls my
precisamente ahí iba me llama muchísimo
attention a lot a lot a lot what [ __ ]
muchísimo muchísimo la atención que
and the defenders of the law and
[__] y los defensores de la ley y
delox where is
delox dónde está
delox and all
delox y todos
the channels that talked
los canales que hablaban
about all the ones he was
de de todas las
going to go to
que iba entrar en la
jail and that they have paraded this one and they
cárcel y que han paseado al ra este y
have uploaded them to their channels and all
los han subido a sus canales y todas
that
esas
stuff a guy who has been
cosas un tío que ha estado todo el fin
in
de semana en la
jail all weekend a guy who has been
cárcel un tío que ha estado todo el fin
in jail all weekend for
de semana en la cárcel por
precisely
precisamente
death threats
muerte
assaults and they have gotten him out for paying
agresiones y lo han sacado por pagar una
bail and they have put a restraining order on him
fianza y le han puesto una orden de
okay tell this to Lili  who
alejamiento vale dielo esto a Lili que
does that who is the one who commands that
es la que hace eso que es la que mandan
okay I'm at the salseria
eso vale estoy la salsería
and this restraining order is true
y esta orden de alejamiento sí es verdad
This arrest is true This
Esta detención sí es verdad Esta
complaint for death threats is
denuncia por amenazas de muerte sí es
true these assaults are
verdad estas agresiones sí son
true and this guy has really gone to
verdad y este tío si ha entrado en la
jail and delox and
cárcel de verdad y delox y
Ricky and gibel and the other one and the one from motto and
Ricky y gibel y el otro y el de motto y
everyone I don't know what's going on But
todos no sé qué pasa
this why not Of course It's that here
Pero esto por qué no Claro Es que aquí
is where you say Look it has to
es donde tú dices Mira es que tiene que
be Dallas if not it doesn't matter it's that this is
ser Dallas si no no importa es que aquí
where it is shown No well I didn't have to
es donde se demuestra No pues no tenía
comment I don't know what about I don't know what
que comentar yo no sé qué de no sé qué
game that didn't matter a [ __ ] [ __ ] the
juego que importaba una [__] [__] la
truth and
verdad y
this where is everyone
esto dónde están todos
anyway it's not clear because of
en fin que no se aclara bien porque
course this guy tells whatever he wants
claro este cuenta lo que le da la gana
apparently in his live he was
por lo visto en su directo estaba
talking about Javi from Dallas he stole it doesn't
hablando de Javi de Dallas robó no
mean that they deen of being
quiere decir que ellos deen de ser unos
[ __ ] scammers [ __ ] that If they
[__] estafadores [__] que Si
were here in the United States and the
estuvieran aquí en Estados Unidos y el
other [ __ ] Fernando
otro mariquito el de de Fernando
Urdaneta wasn't hiding in
urdaneta no estuviera escondiéndose en
Venezuela
Venezuela
hiding in Venezuela hiding in Venezuela I
escondiéndose en
mean they have arrested me for
Venezuela O sea me Han detenido por
death threats and assaults and  there's
amenazas de muerte y agresiones y hay
a lawsuit from a certain night watchman there's a
una demanda de un tal sereno hay una
lawsuit from a certain night watchman who claims that
demanda de un tal sereno que afirma que
this guy doesn't pay his
ese tío No le paga el
rent, or rather, everything they've said about
alquiler o sea todo lo que han dicho de
Dallas in a pack, this guy was
Dallas en un pack este tío
going to take it, the guy was going to say
yba a [__] el tío iba a decir en
live, no, but Dallas, and Daniel Jos
directo no pero Dallas y y Daniel José
wouldn't be putting on chroma keys. But
no estuviera poniéndose cromas Pero
Minoru would be more than in jail, but that one. Yes, he would be in jail
minoru estaría más que preso pero ese Sí
for real, not like me, who
estaría preso de verdad no como yo que
went there to take my statement, that one would
fueron allá a tomarme declaraciones ese
be in jail because he has made
estaría preso porque él ha hecho
explicit threats of shooting
amenazas explícitas de meter tiros de
people to cut their throats. This guy has put you in jail,
de tío que te han metido en la cárcel a
that the restraining order from Dallas
ti que la orden de alejamiento de Dallas
was false, that it didn't exist, that it was an
era falsa que no existía que era una
excuse, paranoia,
excusa paranoia
debate that the one who put you in
debatir que el que te han metido en la
jail is you. Let's see, that, that I
cárcel es a ti a ver que que que yo
understand that in a moment of heat,
entiendo que en un momento de calentón
in a fight or whatever.
en una pelea o lo que sea Pues a lo
Well, maybe the police arrive, stop or
mejor la policía llega se para o lo que
whatever, but for you to Mind, stop, but
sea pero para que te Mentes para pero
for them to put you in jail and for
para que te metan en la cárcel y para
you to be put on bail for 7,500 bucks,
que te pongan una fianza de 7500 pavos
eh, the clues that there are have to be
eh los indicios que hay tienen que ser
curious,
curiosos
I'm not saying, eh, I'm saying  eh eye maybe I'm
no digo yo eh digo yo eh ojo lo mismo me
wrong the police is that over
equivoco la policía es que por
there smokes
allí fuma
joints Yeah but they more than that amazing
porros Sí pero ellos más quo flipante
Hey what's this about 31 new members
Oye qué es eso de que 31 miembros
22 members are missing to reach 3000 what
22 miembros para llegar a los 3000 lo
happens is that of course I would like that
que pasa es que claro me gustaría que en
instead of 22 members we spend it with
vez de 22 miembros lo pasáramos con con
a little bit of hard orgad no so that
un poquito de de orgad dura no para que
tomorrow
mañana no se
others won't have been eliminated a bail of 7500
hayan eliminado otros una fianza de 7500
is not a small thing man already already you'll tell me
no es poca cosa hombre ya ya ya me dirás
no already you'll tell me
no ya me dirás
no 7500 bucks for
no 7500 pavos por
God's sake but it's that Dallas was
Dios no pero es que a Dallas le
sentenced for right to honor in a
condenaron por derecho al honor en una
civil to 6000
civil a 6000
Oops How
Ups Qué
serious to take away legs I mean here Dallas
grave quitarle piernas o sea aquí Dallas
here in the United States would be in prison ha
aquí en Estados Unidos estaría preso ha
Uh many years many years Uh would be would be I mean would
Uh hace muchos años muchos años Uh
be
estaría o sea estaría
Dallas would be I would be in jail Yes
Dallas estaría estaría en la cárcel Sí
yes What happened nothing a little problem there a little
sí Qué pasó nada un problemita ahí un
economic problem Marshall nothing nothing
problemita económico Marshall nada nada
a
un problemita
little economic problem a little economic problem But well thank God we resolved it thank God we are here at home it didn't get any worse it didn't happen it didn't get any worse they put me in
pasó no pasó a mayores me metieron en la
jail nonsense nonsense there are people who
cárcel tontería tontería hay gente que
go to Crdoba on the weekend okay
se va al fin de semana a Córdoba vale
there to a
allí a un
spa this weekend The truth
balneario este fin de semana La verdad
is that things were very expensive
es que estaba la cosa muy carita
drawing what the [ __ ] the
dibujo qu [__] el
B Do that well they grab on to that and
B agan de eso pues se agarran de eso y
Nonsense like nonsense Look at all
Tonterías como que tonterías Mira todos
the videos that are recommended man
los vídeos que le salen recomendados tío
here look the Dallas channel comes up and
aquí mira le sale el canal de Dallas y
a channel about everything related to
le sale un canal de todo relacionado con
Dallas comes up
Dallas
man stupid like that I already because
tío tonter como que ya me porque
obviously I the guy already understood that
obviamente yo el tipo ya ent que que que
the guy was a tremendous scammer I
el [__] era tremendo estafador Yo
start contacting absolutely all
empiezo a contactar absolutamente a toda
his family contact his
su familia contactar a su
brother we will have to see this having
hermano habrá que ver esto habiendo
seen the raay here the ways he
visto al raay aquí las formas que
has man but he counts on them that
tiene hombre pero cuenta con ellos esa
excuse is perfect But well do not enter
excusa está perfect Pero bueno no entres
anymore
más
contacting the family with the
contactando con la familia con los
brothers of a turkey who owed him
hermanos de de un pavo que le debía
money according to
dinero según
him I tried to get the
él trate de conseguir el número de la
mother's number but not to harm them
mamá pero no para hacerles ningún daño
but so that she would help me recover the
sino para que me ayudara a recuperar la
money because so that they would call him and
plata pues para que lo llamaran y le
say Hey look you know what you are You are
dijeran Oye mira sabes qué estás Estás
stealing from a person the person already knows
robando a una persona la persona ya sabe
Who we are so that he feels ashamed well it
Quiénes somos para que le dé vergüenza
is so that he feels ashamed  and the
pues es para que le dé vergüenza y El
guy grabs onto it to say like
tipo se agarra de ahí para decir o sea
I don't even know the mother's name
yo ni siquiera sé cómo se llama la mamá
How can I hurt a person
Cómo le puedo hacer daño a una persona
that I don't even know the
que ni siquiera sé cómo se
name of is impossible I mean I don't know
llama es imposible o sea no sé cómo se
the mother's name the guy I don't know where he lives they're
llama la mamá el tipo no sé dónde vive
not going to put you in jail Simply
no te van a meter la cárcel Simplemente
because a guy okay here you have the bmat
porque un tío vale aquí tenéis el bmat
eh they're not going to put you in jail because
eh no te van a meter en la cárcel porque
a guy
un tío se
makes something up let's see we're talking about a guy who
invente a ver estamos hablando de un tío
made up that dasas had told him
que se inventó que dasas le había dicho
that I was flirting with people on
que yo coqueteaba con la gente por
Instagram okay And that d hired hitmen
Instagram vale Y que d contrató sicarios
for serene and for delox okay I mean
para serene y para delox vale o sea
we're talking about a guy who made
estamos hablando un tipo que se inventó
that up for me the worst thing is not even
eso para mí lo más grave ya no es ni el
Ray himself for me it's the people who
propio Ray para mí es la gente que le
paid attention to him that
dio
man
eso tío el tweet de
delox's tweet well delox's tweet saying
delox bueno el tweet de delox diciendo
that he was going to report what where is
lo de que iba a denunciar qué dónde está
that
esa
report where is that report I mean
denuncia dónde está esa denuncia
for all of you who are
o sea para todos los que están
celebrating that this happened to me
celebrándose que me ocurrió esto
unfortunately well I tell you yes
desgraciadamente pues les digo que si
yes Oh you saw what Dallas said
que si Ah que viste lo que dijo Dallas
Well I tell you yes if Dallas
Pues te digo que si que si Dallas
lived in the United States if I
viviera en los Estados Unidos si yo que
only  I told the person
solamente le dije a la persona hoy esta
tonight you won't be able to be calm in
noche no vas a poder estar tranquilo en
your house and I didn't mean that I was going to
tu casa y no me refería que yo lo fuera
look for him but that the police were going to
a buscar sino que la policía lo iba a
look for him and they are trying to
buscar y me y me están tratando a mí de
put me in jail imagine with a person
dejar preso imagínense con una persona
who told me that he was going to shoot me twice
que me dijo a mí que me iba a meter dos
and stab me twice don't celebrate
tiros y dos puñaladas que no celebre
too much Dallas because Dallas with the
mucho Dallas porque Dallas con los
messages that he sent me I would be in
mensajes que me mandó a mí aquí estaría
jail anyway so what's celebrating
preso igual así que que es celebrar
[ __ ] because it's more they make that up, I mean
pendejada porque es más se inventan eso
in the in the case they make it up, I mean Look at
o sea en la en el caso se inventan o sea
this Look at this stuff what are they
Mira esta Mira esta vaina qué es lo que
saying around
dicen por
here look written threats or rather threats
aquí mira written threats o sea amenazas
written threats to kill incredible
amenazas por escritas de matar increíble
written threats to kill or to or to
amenaza por escrita de matar o de o de
cause physical harm that didn't happen and
hacer un daño físico eso no pasó y
no that didn't happen the police made it up
no eso no pasó se le ha inventado la
okay that didn't happen well that didn't happen that didn't happen Don't
vale eso no pasó pues eso no pasó eso no
worry because very
de No te preocupes que dentro de muy
soon you're going to
poco vas a
end up worry that you're going to end up in
terminar preocupes que vas a terminar en
[ __ ] jail very soon don't
la [__] cárcel muy pronto tranquilo no
worry very soon you're going to end up in
te preocupes muy pronto vas a terminar
[ __ ] jail I assure you that all the
la [__] cárcel te aseguro que todas las
[ __ ] that you've done we already have it all
[__] que has hecho ya lo tenemos todo
recorded  the
registrado termin la
[ __ ] piece of [ __ ] [ __ ] don't
put pedazo de cabrón de [__] no te
hurt me don't worry let me teach you
prup no te preocupes que enseñ
no no
t no no
who c enci because a [ __ ] scammer like
qui c enci porque un [__] estafador como
you tell me that I'm going to leave I don't
tú me digas a m que yo me voy a salir no
want to talk to you
quiero hablar contigo
brother [ __ ] off and stop saying that I
brother la [__] boca y deja decir que yo
have you scared because you're the one who's
te tengo a ti miedo que tú lo que das
laughable
risa
moral to tell anyone else scammer
moral para decirle a más nadie estafador
Shut your mouth Go to your channel
Cállate la boca Vete a tu canal
conas you're one yes we'll see something too
conas eres una yos veremos algo también
poc
poc
my face twisting with laughter face
mi cara revolviéndose de la risa cara
twisting with laughter delos has
revolviéndose de la risa delos ha
shut up I don't know what's wrong with him you saw
callado no sé queé le pasa del viste
these threats Look this was this is
estas amenazas Mira esta fue este es
delox this is Ray's relationship with
delox esta es la relación de Ray con
delox
delox
before r invents the hitmen thing
antes de que r se invente lo de los
okay on top of that because a [ __ ] scammer
vale encima porque un [__] estafador
like you tell me that I'm going to leave I do
como tú me digas a m que yo me voy a
n't want to talk to you brother
salir no quiero hablar contigo brother
no [ __ ] off and stop saying that I
no la [__] boca y deja de decir que yo
have you scared because you're the one who's
te tengo a ti miedo que tú lo que das es
laughable scammer you have no moral to tell
risa estafa no tienes moral para decirle
anyone else scammer Shut your mouth
a más nadie estafador Cállate la boca
Go to your channel with
Vete a tu canal con
me don't say anything you're one This was
tengo no digas nada eres una Esto fue
first then  r started saying this
primero luego r empezó a decir esta
nonsense and contacted delox and
tontería y contactó con delox y se
the two of them made up this story these
inventaron los dos este rollo estos
hitman is hiring a hitman no you in
sicario está contratar sicario no tú en
that house saw these threats how well
esa casa viste estas amenazas que bueno
these hitman is hiring a hitman no
estos sicario está contratar cicario no
because and how am I going to see the hitmen
porque y cómo voy a ver yo los cicarios
and I'm going to see things in that house it has to do with
y voy a ver cosas en esa casa tiene que
what do you think it is that I was
ver qué crees tú que es que yo estaba
there was chili El Topo And that's what that's what they
allá estaba el chili El Topo Y eso lo
're telling Let's see you
eso es lo que están contando A ver tú
have one those cones cont nothing yes but let's
tienes una eso conos cont nada sí pero a
see that delo told it after having
ver eso lo contó delo después de tener
a conversation with you on discord and
una conversación contigo por discord y
you what and you as a conclusion you come out that I
tú có y tú como conclusión sacas que yo
was the one who gave it to delo right let's
fui el que le dio a delo right vamos a
see Rey I you know that with you I have
ver Rey yo tú sabes queo contigo tengo
nothing it's a problem you with him but And
nada es problema tu con él pero Y tú
as a conclusion you come out that I told
como conclusión sacas que yo se lo dije
delox I'm seeing you that you ca
a delox yo te estoy viendo a ti que tú
n't stand delo the other day
al delo no lo soportas el otro día
When you get on a call with gibel and
Cuando subes en una llamada con gibel y
with Ricky you don't even want to be put
con Ricky tú no quieres ni que te metan
with him on a call and suddenly I see you
con él en llamada y de repente te veo
yesterday that you have spoken with delox in the
ayer que has hablado con delox en las
last hours and delo comes out saying that that he
últimas horas y sale delo diciendo que
has a  some hitmen behind
que que tiene una unos sicario detrás
him how clumsy they are and that
suya qué torpe son y que se le ha
someone has told him that he was in the house they
contado alguien de que estaba en la casa
always show all their cards man they are
enseñan todas sus cartas siempre tío son
super duper that's what Quiz Quiz said
super tontos eso es lo que dijo Quiz
hab drawn conclusions Not that what he
Quiz hab sacado conclusiones No eso que
said give them put do you want to put prun
lo diga deles poner quieres poner prun
let's do another way give it more turn give it
vamos hacer ot manera dale más vuel dale
more Vu my mom please
más Vu mi mam por
[Laughter]
[Risas]
estanos Look at the conversations of the one from the
estanos Mira las conversaciones del del
RAE
RAE
[Laughter]
[Risas]
[Music]
[Música]
man And from there delox changed his
tío Y a partir de ahí delox cambió su
attitude with red to this enter entered delo
actitud con red a esto entr entró delo
before anything of the and such because so a
antes de nada de los y tal porque así un
little behind the back I think that r should
poco por la espalda creo que r debería
know that you are here that maybe no no no I didn't want
saber que estás aquí que a lo mejor no
wanted to say one thing
no no no quería quería decir una cosa
only if I am here Well I am sobad
solo si yo estoy aquí Bueno estoy sobad
simo it's It's simple here can't noon the
simo es Es simple aquí no puede noon la
camera the camera I have to connect it
cámara la cámara tengo que conectarla
bastard is with the Nutella bastard fado
cabón está con la nutella cabrón fado
with the Nutella with that he didn't want it to
con la nutella con que no quería que
be del I have nothing to do
estuviera del tengo nada que
yoed I just wanted a question and I'm
ver yoed Solo quería una pregunta y me
going don't worry about him because I
voy no te preocupes el porque yo te
'm listening to you and I tell you [ __ ] this r I'm
estoy escuchando y te digo [__] este r
starting to like him you know then I
me empieza a caer bien sabes entonces
say  [ __ ] Why don't you want me to
digo [__] Por qué no quiere que
be
esté
and like
e como
uh he has taken it upon himself to make the
eh se ha encargado de hacer pública la
other side public once again constantly you can't
otra parte una vez más constantemente no
silence an accusation uh
se puede callar una acusación eh
exaggeratedly serious and and well and Well
exageradamente grave y y bueno y Bueno
in fact also criminal
de hecho también delictiva
and also surreal uh however
y también surrealista eh sin embargo yo
at that same moment I already made uh I posted a
en ese mismo momento ya hice eh puse un
tweet in which I was trying to appeal to I do
tweet en el cual intentaba apelar a
n't know a last Abyss of conscience in
no sé un último Abismo de consciencia en
that person telling him that well that he's
en esa persona diciéndole que bueno que
basically going crazy and that in the end I'm not the
básicamente y que al final yo no soy la
person who is constantly threatening to
persona que se dedica a amenazar de
kill everyone every day
muerte constantemente cada día a todo el
or that he's made videos directly
mundo o que ha hecho vídeos directamente
uh fantasizing about how to torture and
eh fantaseando sobre cómo torturar y
murder in the most is still in
asesinaría de la forma más es todavía es
recent weeks and has been like
últimas semanas y ha estado como
taking up a lot of unbearable time Oh
ocupando mucho tiempo insoportable Ay
This is not the Or
Este no es el
yes they never end taking up a lot of
O sí no se terminan nunca ocupando mucho
time this character a few
tiempo este personaje hace unas
weeks ago completely normal because
semanas completamente normal porque
well he had no proof of it and
bueno no tenía pruebas de ello y
weeks never end in charge
semanas no se terminan nunca encargado
of doing you already know that last week
de hacer ya sabréis que la semana pasada
This is not the cl no s for puts this
Este no es el cl no s por pone este
text because this is not the But well
texto porque este no es el Pero bueno
myy also put that I
miy también puso
value  a lot of my life if for whatever reason I
que valoro mucho mi vida si por lo que
disappear or you see that I stop making
sea desaparezco o veis que dejo de hacer
content it won't be under my will they
contenido no será bajo mi voluntad le
gave veracity to
dieron veracidad a
ra it was Ricky No no there were a few
ra fue Ricky No no fueron unos cuantos
miad Ricky there were a few anyway
miad Ricky fueron unos cuantos en fin
[ __ ] But in what a short time
[__] Pero en qué poco tiempo
eh In what a short time man this movie has changed
eh En qué poco tiempo tío ha cambiado
and dasas also said something in a
y dasas ha dicho algo también en un
live Thank you alus very much and no I haven't
directo Gracias alus muchísima y no no
had the opportunity I was working
he tenido oportunidad estab trabajando
too much I want to want to see because I
demasiado Quiero quiero ver porque me
want to set up a new studio and I'm
quiero montar un estudio nuevo y estoy
going crazy to see how I set it up I
volviéndome loco para ver có lo monto
would like to set up one that had a
gustaría montar uno que fuese con una
podcast area to be able to do some
zona para podcast para poder hacer algo
podcast with it I would also like to
de podcast con l también me gustaría
do it I'm there tied up with a ton of
hacerlo estoy ahí liado con un montón de
things and it's driving me crazy
cosas y me tiene loco
guima many porbl and mercur basically I did
guima muchas porbl y mercur básicamente
n't want to give him any more at that moment and that's it that
no quería darle más en ese momento y ya
was it in essence that was
está eso fue todo en esencia eso fue
all but well the jerk came to
todo pero bueno el el caraso le vino al
this clown Aoki sincerely the same as
payaso este Aoki sinceramente igual que
many others who are there I think they will have
ha muchos otros que está ahí Creo que le
asked him in the chat for
habrán preguntado en el chat por
haplo with a criminal record or
haplo con antecedentes penales o en la
directly in jail people who spent their time
cárcel directamente gente que se la pasó
harassing me and that right now they
acosándome a full Y que ahora mismo
are sentenced  with a
están condenados con antecedentes
criminal record or directly in prison
penales o directamente en prisión
literally in prison
literalmente en prisión
Eh well eh rom very handsome I love you a
Eh bueno eh romá guapísimo te qui un
lot I send you a kiss Grand beautiful
montón te mando un bes Grand precioso de
really Thank you very much for the tip I know
verdad Muchísimas gracias por el tip se
a lot rom eh And if
un montón romá eh Y si
crazy like many who dedicated themselves to telling me
loquísimo como muchos que se dedicaron a
a lot of garbage to me and now you
decme un montón de basura a mí y ahora
are in jail literally I am not
estás en la cárcel literal no estoy
literally and others who are going to be
literalmente y otros que van a estar
very
pronto muy
strong soon I do not know who you are referring to with
fuerte no sé a quién se refiere con
others I know that he has filed complaints and things
otros se que ha puesto denuncias y cosas
but for jail tasty old man did you see the
pero para cárcel viejo sabroso viste lo
new
nuevo de
coscu yes we will see it now we will see it
coscu sí lo vamos a ver ahora lo vamos a
now I will see what he thinks here
ver ahora voy a ver qué opina por aquí
the compel
el compel
life like my Telegram group
la vida como mi grupo de de Telegram
knows I have been having a problem for
sabe vengo teniendo un problema hace
about a week with a
aproximadamente una semana con una
person who now I cannot name by
persona que ahora no puedo nombrar con
name and surname because obviously he
nombre y apellido porque obviamente
has a
tiene una orden de
restraining order this stupid because
alejamiento este estupidísima porque
obviously I am not going to do
obviamente yo no voy a hacer
absolutely nothing But this person
absolutamente nada Pero esta persona me
robbed me head on head on head on
robó de frente de frente de frente
50,000 eh but head on Well head on going around in circles I did
50,000 eh pero de frente Pues de frente
not want to go to I did not want to
dándole vueltas no quería ir a no quería
go to the bank When when Supposedly I
ir al banco Cuando cuando Supuestamente
was going to return the money he left me
iba regresar el dinero me dejaba
stranded what video  is this gbel very
plantado qué vídeo es este gbel muy
sad I don't
triste
know what I don't know I don't know what I saw it's been two
no no sé qué no sé no sé qué vi es dos
days in a row he left me standing at the
días seguidos me dejó plantado en el
bank this guy made me go for the wait
banco este me hizo ir a for la esperar
in a restaurant that supposedly was
en un restaurante que supuestamente
going to arrive and never arrived he had a
lleba a llegar y nunca llegó tenía un
supposed Russian partner who was himself
supuesto socio ruso que era él mismo
answering the call and doing
contestando la llamada y haciendo
accents or rather a lot of madness the
acentos o sea un montón de locura el
guy stopped not to not return the money
tipo para no para no volver el dinero
What happens is that I got married and I managed to get his
Qué pasa que yo me avé y yo logré que le
account blocked before he
bloquearan la cuenta antes de que
could withdraw the money no Steven do
pudiera sacar el dinero en no Steven tú
you think Dallas can take
te piensas que Dallas puede llevar a
root to
raiz a la
jail I suppose not I suppose not
cárcel supongo que no supongo que no
this is because of an issue of a threat that
esto es por un tema de una amenaza que
rz wrote to a person who
rz escribió a una persona que
supposedly stole 50,000 from him and that he he
supuestamente le robó 50,000 y que él él
went to the police station and ended up well
fue a comisaría y terminó pues
in jail ended up detained for this
encarcelado terminó retenido por esto
So they blocked his account but they didn't
Entonces le bloquearon la cuenta pero no
want to keep it blocked until
se la querían mantener bloqueada hasta
I had a police report
tanto yo no tuviera un reporte policial
of uh informing me of what
de eh informando lo que me había heicho
the guy had done to me well enough I'm going to a
el tipo bueno basta que me voy a a un
police department in one of the
departamento de policía de una de la
cities here in Miami I'm
ciudades aquí en Miami estoy toda la
there all afternoon practically all afternoon
tarde prácticamente ahí toda la tarde
well helping giving these statements
bueno ayudando dando este declaraciones
about how the guy had stolen from me
acerca de cómo el tipo me había robado
how much he had taken from me blah blah blah blah
de cuánto me había quitado bla bla bla
well it turns out that the guy while
bla bueno resulta que el tipo mientras
I Yes today there will be a video on the
yo Sí hoy habrá vídeo en el canal
main channel I'm there at the police station
principal estoy ahí en la comisaría
starts saying that
empieza a decir que supuestamente
supposedly allegedly What happened with the
presuntamente Qué ha pasado con la
Dallas class action lawsuit the truth is
demanda colectiva de Dallas la verdad
that I don't
que no lo
know nobody knows no I hope it's not
sé nadie lo sabe no Espero que no sean
the parents the truth Because we've been left hanging
los padres la verdad Porque nos han
never but hanging Why man I mean
nunca me pero con la miel en los labios
why would you be happy
Por qué tío o sea por qué te alegrarías
about said in theory it was going to come out in
tú por dicho en teoría iba a salir en
November the last one you told me in
noviembre el último que me dijisteis por
the chat in November But if it was if it was in September it's already in
el chat en noviembre Pero si era si era
November but
en septiembre ya va por noviembre pero
if it was in September in August it was in September it's
si era en septiembre en agosto era en
already November okay they had
septiembre ya es noviembre vale de que
commented that November was going to
habían comentado que noviembre iba a
come to light Yes
salir a la luz Sí
yes but the class action lawsuit was It was a
sí pero la demanda colectiva era Era una
metaphor it was a metaphor a metaphor
metáfora era una metáfora una metáfora
that I just made up a metaphor
que me acabo de inventar una metáfora
How are things going I
Cómo va la cosa yo lo
had it Oh we still have to explain Where
había Ay todavía hay que explicar Dónde
is the class action lawsuit we
está la demanda colectiv
still have to explain Who is RAE we
todavía hay que explicar Quién es RAE
still have to explain Who is
todavía hay que explicar Quién es
delox roasted with doing something to him physically
delox asado con hacerle algo físicamente
something that never happened I mean I never
cosa que nunca ocurrió o sea nunca le
told him you  I'm going to do this, I'm going to do that to you, the
dije te voy a hacer esto te voy a hacer
only thing I explicitly
lo otro lo único que explícitamente le
told him was this, I'm at the police station, I
dije fue este estoy en la policía le
sent him a picture to the police station, I
mandé una foto a la estación de policía
'm at the police station, and I think you
estoy en la policía y yo creo que ya hoy
won't be able to sleep at your house today, but I
no llegas a dormir a tu casa pero yo
never told him because I was one,
nunca se lo dije porque yo lo fuera o
meaning what put Raiz
sea lo que hizo que raiz estuviese
in jail was telling him this, and I think you
encarcelado fue decirle esto y yo creo
won't be able to sleep at your house today,
que ya hoy no llegas a dormir a tu casa
but I never told him because I
pero yo nunca se lo dije porque yo lo
went looking for him, meaning the
fuera a buscar o sea la línea
space-time line according to Commenta ra is that
espaciotemporal según Comenta ra es que
he goes to a police station in Miami to
él va a una comisaría de Miami a
report a guy who supposedly
denunciar a un tipo que supuestamente le
stole $50,000 from him,
robó $50,000
while he's at the police station, he writes to
mientras está en la comisaría escribe a
this guy and to the guy, they don't do anything to him with $
este y al tío No le hacen nada con
50,000, meaning raay, he's supposed to
50.000 pavos o sea raay se supone que
have proof of those $50,000
tiene que tener pruebas de esos 50,000
that they stole from him,
que le han robado de esas llamadas
making excuses, and they don't do anything to the guy, they
poniendo excusas y al tío No le hacen
arrested Ra because he made
nada detienen a ra porque le ha hecho
a
una
threat, come on,
amenaza anda por
please, anonymous kid, you're
favor chico anónimo
not sleeping in your bed today, no, you're not sleeping
hoy no duermes en tu cama no no duermes
at your house, but I never sent a
en tu casa pero yo nunca me mandé una
picture to myself.  to the police station I'm at
foto a la estación de policía estoy en
the police station and I think that you won't be able
la policía y yo creo que ya hoy no
to sleep at your house today but and this
llegas a dormir a tu casa pero y esto
made the guy I was
hizo que el chico al que estaba
reporting report him for
denunciando le denuncie por
threats anyway I never told him because
amenazas fin yo nunca se lo dije porque
I was going to look for him or because I was going to
yo lo fuera buscar o porque yo fuer a
do any kind of harm to him so the
hacerle ningún tipo de daño entonces El
guy grabs onto that message to say
tipo se agarra de ese mensaje para decir
that I wanted that I was
que yo quería que yo lo estaba
threatening him with me going to look for him to
amenazando con yo irlo a buscar a
do something to him and the police from the
hacerle algo y los de la policía del
police department from there what they
departamento de policia de ahí lo que
did instead of going to look for the guy
hicieron en vez de ir a buscar al tipo
who stole the 50,000 from me was arrest
que me robó los 50,000 fue detenerme a
me because I told him in a message that I was
mí porque le dije mensaje que hoy en la
n't coming home tonight because he
noche no llegaba a su casa porque
probably went to L the police how do
probablemente se I a L la policía cómo
you think how do you think let's see according to
les parece cómo les parece a ver según
what you say it's at least comical the
lo comenta es cuanto menos cómico la
truth according to how you are commenting it
verdad según cu como lo está comentando
is comical it's the great great huge
es cómico es el gran gran grandísimo
impressive crime that I committed that they
impresionante delito que cometí yo que
stole 50,000 from me and that the guy who
me robaran 50,000 y que el tipo que me
robbed me I told him that no no no it's a lie
robó le dije que que no no no es mentira
because in what it says here a kiss
porque en en lo que pone aquí un beso
Vero Can someone pass me these audios
Vero Alguien me puede pasar los audios
that the  nauter flay that he
estos que publicó la nauter flay que que
took out the
sacó la
ex of
la ex de
r come on but not only
r vamos pero no solamente los audios
those audios but right here once I
esos sino que aquí mismo una vez me
remember that he donated and the donation itself
acuerdo que donó y la propia donación
was [ __ ] crazy that I had to
era una [__] locura que le tuve que
tell him dude
decir yo tío
calm down I mean if to me from the first
Cálmate O sea si a mí yo desde el primer
moment from the first day when I saw
momento desde el primer día yo cuando vi
this guy I
a este tipo a m las formas con las que
didn't like the way he went and everything I respected him
iba y demás no me gustaba lo respetaba
he was a friend of
era amigo del
Dallas or a partner or colleague what the [ __ ] and I
Dallas o socio o colega qué [__] fuera y
had respect for him That's why but mm
le tenía respeto Por eso pero mm
dude what the [ __ ] is the black bull dude they
chico qué [__] es el toro negro tío me
're all putting me
están poniendo todos
in the tweet that I put to Messi
en el tweet que le he puesto al Messi
[ __ ] you are always going to be the
[__] eres un siempre serás el toro
black bull what the [ __ ] is that someone
negro qué [__] es eso alguien me lo
can explain to me well what they are saying around
puede explicar bien qué es lo que dicen
here in what it says here it says the
por aquí en lo que pone aquí pone el
charge write death threats
cargo escribir amenazas de muerte
slander let's see the police don't take it for that
injuria a ver la policía no coge por por
reason I'm going to put nobody in jail I
eso I va a meter la cárcel a nadie yo
obviously don't live in the United
evidentemente no vivo en los Estados
States I don't know what it will be But
Unidos no sé cómo será Pero
[Music]
[Música]
dude more than anything out of
chico más que nada por
logic for slander not for threats it
lógica por injurias no por amenazas no
has nothing to do with the 00000
tiene nada que ver con lo de los 00000
we'll see how all this ends
veremos a ver cómo acaba todo esto la
thing is surreal to say the least the thing
cosa es surrealista cuanto menos la cosa
is surreal right now a
es surrealista en este momento una orden
restraining order the guy I can't say his
de alejamiento el tipo no puedo decir su
name has a restraining order
nombre tiene una orden de alejamiento
As he said
Como dijo
before the same for those who For those who
antes igual para los que Para los que me
follow me on Instagram already know who it is
siguen en instagram ya saben quién es
because then the issue is that dasas
porque ya luego el tema es que dasas
seeing this has posted a
viendo esto ha puesto un comentario
rather curious comment saying the following
bastante curioso diciendo lo siguiente
is eating crazy the slightest thing he goes
está meal loquito a la mínima se vuelve
crazy and starts
loco y se pone a
saying outrageous things He is really
decir barbaridades Realmente está
sick seeing this has posted a
enfermo viendo esto ha puesto un
rather curious comment saying the
comentario bastante curioso diciendo lo
following is eating
siguiente está
crazy you can give his name
loquito ti pued de su nombre ord de
restraining order same for Instagram you know that
alejamiento igual para Instagram saben
Hey esend this is
Oye esend estoo
saying the following is eating crazy the
diciendo lo siguiente está meal loquito
slightest thing he goes crazy and starts
a la mínima se vuelve loco y se pone a
saying outrageous things He is really
decir barbaridades Realmente está
sick the thing is why is this why they
enfermo la cosa es por qué Por esto lo
deported him from the USA no dude it's that t t you
deportan de USA no tío es que t t no
can't say this How come if they
puedes decir esto Cómo que no si lo
deport him they deport him Of course they
condan lo deportan Claro que lo
deported him in the United States a
deportan en Estados Unidos un tío
Venezuelan guy was convicted of
venezolano lo condenan por amenazas de
death threats and assaults of course
muerte y agresiones claro
obviously they didn't convict him I'm not saying that if they
obvio no lo condenaron No digo que si lo
convict him that's from an anime called
condenan eso es de un anime llamado
Black clovers watch it me  I imagine it will be
Black clovers mírelo me imagino que será
things like that but I'm not
cosas de esas pero que que no os estoy
asking you what cartoon it is but
preguntando de qué dibujito es sino que
what is it that the black bull does the
qué es lo que hace el toro negro lo de
black bull is a reference to a
toro negro es una referencia un anime
very good anime yes basically it
buenísimo eso sí que básicamente
means that you friend that they think that you are straying they think that you are
significa que te amigo que creen que
straying from the path for continuing dala and
desviado del camino por seguira dala y
one day you will reconsider and join the
algún día vas a recapacitar y unirte al
group no qu What's going on what's
grupo no qu Va qué va qu
going on you can say this you can't say
va puedes decir esto no puedes decir
this when for that very reason they just put
esto cuando tú por eso mismo que acaban
ra in jail you would have a
de meter preso raí tú tendrías una
bail of 000 man don't [ __ ] with me that you said that you
fianza 000 tío no me jodas que dijiste
wanted to rip someone's arm off
que querías arrancarle un brazo a una
Oh really if he's a citizen there's no way to get
persona Ay de verdad si es ciudadano no
him out of there
hay quien lo saque de ahí
if he's a citizen even if he's a
si es ciudadano aunque
migrant because he's a migrant No what did he
sea migrante porque es migrante No qué
say here this when you
es lo que ha dicho aquí esto cuando tú
for that very reason they just put
por eso mismo que acaban de de meter
ra in jail you would have a bail of
preso a raí tú tendrías una fianza de de
000 man don't [ __ ] with me that you said that you
000 tío no me jodas que dijiste que
wanted to rip someone's arm off
querías arrancarle un brazo una persona
or that if he crossed you he would end up in the
o que si te lo cruzaba acababa en el
cemetery and then the millor  of
cementerio y luego lo del millor de los
friends d if I lived in the United States and
amigos d si viviera en Estados Unidos y
a person from the United States reported me, they
le denunciar una persona de Estados
would be the same as weird, worse
Unidos estarían las mismas que rao peor
guy, I don't know, I don't know, man, I don't know, well,
tío es que no sé no sé tío no lo sé
or maybe I wouldn't do it or we'll have to
bueno o a lo mejor no lo haría o habrá
see what he
que ver qué es lo que le ha
said, we'll have to see what
dicho habrá que ver qué es lo que é ha
the previous one said, anyway, they don't deport him,
dicho el anterior en fin no lo deportan
the crime was in the United States, yes, but yes, if
el delito fue en Estados Unidos sí pero
you
si si tú
are a citizen of the United States who
eres ciudadano de los Estados Unidos que
comes from outside,
viene de fuera
no, you tell me that to my face and you're like Goyo,
no tú me dices eso la cara y te de Goyo
but he doesn't realize, he doesn't
pero es que no se da cuenta no se da
realize. Ah, it's that it's the country's fault, is it
cuenta Ah es que es elas del
true? Karime says Javi, in the USA it doesn't
verdad dice Karime Javi en USA no
work like you say, if he committed the
funciona como dices si él cometió el
crime in the United States and even worse, an
delito en Estados Unidos y peor aún a un
American citizen has to
ciudadano americano ahí tiene que
serve his
cumplir su
sentence, yes, but what I'm referring to
condena sí pero a lo que me ref cuando
when we talk about
hablamos cuando hablamos de
deportation, what I understand
deportar lo que yo entiendo
is when, let's see. I understand that
es cuando a ver Es que yo entiendo que
this sentence will not be jail,
esta condena no será de cárcel
no, I mean, this sentence, I don't think it's
no o sea esta condena no creo que sea
a jail sentence of serving years in
una condena de cárcel de cumplir años de
jail. I understand that then he can't
cárcel entiendo que luego no puede
continue living in the United States. No,
seguir en los Estados Unidos viviendo No
if he has this,
si tiene esto
no, I'm not explaining myself, right?  well
no no me estoy explicando verdad O sea
I'm not talking to see if they convict him
yo no hablo a ver si lo condenan
obviously he has to serve the
evidentemente tiene que cumplir la
sentence
pena
but once he serves that sentence if the
pero una vez que cumpla esa pena si la
sentence is to be in jail for a few days
pena es de estar unos días en la cárcel
a few months a week or it's a fine or
unos meses una semana o es una multa o
whatever okay then they let you live in
lo que sea vale luego te dejan vivir en
the United
los Estados
States with
Unidos con
that if he's a citizen yes he can continue
eso si es ciudadano sí puede seguir
living there well I have my doubts
viviendo ahí bueno yo tengo mis dudas
about that but you guys will know more
respecto a eso pero ustedes sabren más
than
que
me I'm a migrant if he has citizenship he
yo yo soy migrante siel tiene ciudadanía
won't leave
no se va
mm
mm
well that's what the Dallas of the past said it does
bueno eso lo dijo el Dallas del pasado
n't count it doesn't count the Dallas of the
no cuenta no cuenta el Dallas del
present is a completely
presente es otra persona completamente
different person his name is r helmi literally
diferente se llama r helmi literalmente
like oh my god and they literally
como Ay Dios mío y literalmente le
have to do an urgent help me the
tienen que hacer un help me urgente el
name fits him like a glove luar says if
nombre le va ni pintado luar dice si
he has a visa yes they can take it away if he
está con visa sí se la pueden quitar si
's a citizen it's as if he were from there and
es ciudadano es como si fuera de allí y
raed What is he a citizen or with a visa
raed Qué es ciudadano o con visa
how long does it
cuánto tiempo
take to be one of his jokes as an H of 31
lleva ser una de sus bromas de H de 31
years old my goodness my goodness is that dude you can't
añitos madre mía madre mía es que tío no
say this dude you can't say
puedes decir esto tío no puedes decir
this you're projecting yourself he's mega
esto te te estás proyectando está mega
crazy at the slightest thing he goes crazy and
loquito a la mínima se vuelve loco y se
starts saying outrageous things but dude if you
pone decir barbaridades pero tío si tú
're the first if you're the first or
eres el primero si tú eres el primero o
be for all those who are
sea para todos los que están
celebrating that this happened to me
celebrándose que me ocurrió esto
unfortunately
desgraciadamente
don't comment ra's best friend I'm going to
no comenta el mejor amigo de ra voy a
comment something I find it hard to believe his version
comentar algo me cuesta creer su versión
because he sent it because I find it hard to believe
porque él mandó porque me cuesta creer
his
su
version Well it's hard for me eh I find it hard to believe it eh I'm trying it's hard for me it's hard for me I
versión Bueno me cuesta eh Me cuesta
'm trying but I find it
me cuesta lo estoy intentando pero me
a little hard to believe his version
cuesta un poco creer su versión
eh I'm not very convinced of his
eh No estoy yo muy convencido de su
version he sent it it can't be misinterpreted
versión mando no se puede malinterpretar
more if he sent it from the police station for
más si lo manda desde la comisaría para
me He said something else and he doesn't say it I
mí Le dijo algo más y no lo dice yo
support ra But he is very explosive I
banco a ra Pero él es muy explosivo yo
support raed's phrase but Dallas
banco a raed la frase pero Dallas nunca
was never as alive as it is now XD no no it's not like that can you
estuvo tan viva como ahora XD no no es
imagine if it were the other way around not even if he stepped foot in
así se imaginan si fuera al revés ya ni
jail with
siquiera que pisara la cárcel con la
just the complaint how these
sola denuncia como estarían estos
sick crazy people would be but they are not proving
enfermos de locos pero no están probando
that they only care about the who and not the
que solo les importa el quién y no el
what I support ra his
queé yo banco a
fame rose since he is in
ra le subió la fama desde que está en
the squid games he is not the same he is not the same he is not the
los squid games ya no es el mismo ya no
same he is
es el mismo ya no es el mismo
not the same subscribe if
ya no es el mismo suscríbete si es que
you
te
like it
gusta
eh I don't know I don't know but let's see
eh No lo sé No lo sé pero a ver
surreal no  7500 for putting
surrealista no 7500 por ponerle a
7500 bucks on someone I have my doubts that they
alguien 7500 pavos Yo tengo mi duda de
put them on you simply because of what you
que te los pongan simplemente por eso
're saying, that they took it out of
que está diciendo que lo hayan sacado de
context without any proof, I
contexto sin ninguna prueba
have my doubts right? You know, maybe it
tengo mi duda verdad tú que a lo mejor
's a country with very few
es un país muy poco
guarantees and at the slightest thing they put you in
garantista y ante la mínima te meten en
jail, someone comes along and says, look,
la cárcel llega a uno y dice No mira
look, hey,
mira
tonight don't sleep at your house
eh esta noche no duermas en tu casa
because you're filing a complaint against him
porque estás poniéndole una denuncia
because he stole 50,000 from you. It's weird, not
porque te ha robado 50,000 Es raro no
because all the police could you
porque toda la policía le podrías
explain the context of that. No, I
explicar el contexto de eso no yo eso no
'm not putting that on him because I want to
se lo estoy poniendo porque lo quiera
kill him, but because I'm at
matar sino porque estoy ahora mismo en
the police station right now filing a complaint. I
la comisaría poniéndole la denuncia Yo
'm with gbel, I think there's something more, it's
estoy con gbel creo que hay algo más
not that I think it's too crazy, it
no es que me parece demasiado loco me
seems too crazy to me, they're making that up, I mean,
parece demasiado loco inventan eso o sea
in this case they're making that up, I mean, look, look at
en el caso se inventan o sea mira mira
this stuff, what are they saying around here?
esta vaina qué es lo que dicen por aquí
Look, RS, he's threatening, he's threatening in writing to
mira RS sea amenaz amenaz por escrita de
kill, incredible written threat to
matar increíble amenaza por escrita de
kill or or to cause physical harm, that didn't
matar o o de hacer un daño físico eso no
happen and no, that didn't happen. I don't know. I don't know what
pasó y no eso no pas No lo sé No lo sé
you told me that someone else put it on.  tweet let's
que me dijisteis que ra puso otro tweet
see what the hell is with the funa Okay
a ver qué [__] es lo de la funa Bueno
let's see what the duki thing is first now
vamos a ver primero lo de duki ahora
we see the funa czu Okay I'm going to read this
vemos la funa czu Vale Voy a leer este
thread to find out what happened with
hilo para enterarme qu ha pasado con
ducky because let's go if it's true that he
ducky porque vamos como sea verdad que
cheated on Emilia clar
le ha puesto los cuernos a Emilia clar
Emilia clar Emilia clar is from game
Emilia clar Emilia clar es la de juegoo
of thrones Emilia mernes who is really cute
de Trono Emilia mernes que es monísima
also the girl I don't know how she can
adems la chavala yo no sé cómo puede
be with this man okay scandal
estar con con este hombre vale escándalo
infidelity everything about
infidelidad todo sobre la supuesta
ducky's alleged infidelity Emilia chat audios
infidelidad de ducky Emilia chat audios
videos and intimate photos Hey luare but
vídeos y fotos íntimas Oye luare pero
here's something that makes me want to get
aquí hay algo que me que me vaya a salir
a dick too or
una [__] también o
what a nice ass
qué lindo culito
pretty
lindos
eyes here ducky with a
ojitos aquí ducky con una
girl It all started when they started
chica Todo comenzó cuando comenzaron a
canceling ducky because of Valencia and
cancelar a ducky por lo de valencia y
the donations a lot of people showed up to
las donaciones mucha gente apareció para
cancel it and among these was this
cancelarlo y entre estas estaba esta
girl who claimed to have a duky chat
chica que decía tener chat de duky
asking for nudes what has
pidiéndole nudes qué es lo que ha hecho
duy done with
duy con
Valencia Well I'm uploading it here my friend
Valencia Bueno lo subo acá mi amiga no
was neither slow nor lazy but she forced me
fue ni lenta ni perezosa pero me obligó
to upload the evidence  we may be many things
a subir las pruebas seremos muchas cosas
but not
pero no
liars this girl uploaded a tiktok
mentirosas esta chica subió un tiktok
where she shows a video with
donde muestra un vídeo con el perfil de
duky's profile and the supposed chat many people
duky y los supuestos chat mucha gente
believe that it is rigged and other people
cree que está trucado y otras personas
believe that it is true luare have you
creen que es verdad luare tú lo has
checked it
comprobado
man it does not
hombre no
have if this is rigged it is very well
tiene si esto está trucado está muy bien
rigged
trucado
eh
eh
man if this is rigged it is not
hombre si esto está trucado
fake it is not
fake no es
fake also evidence came out where is I to
fake también salieron pruebas donde is I
which went to Mexico at the beginning of the
a el cual fue a México a principios de
year hired some VIP cats and
año contrató unos gatos VIP y se ve a
duky is seen with another girl we know that there was also
duky con otra chica sabemos que también
drugs
drog
of is him
of es él
no that it is more likely that an editor of
no que es más probable que un editor de
the host has falsified that
la [__] haya falseado eso
perfectly or that the clown of dukin
perfectamente o que el payaso de dukin
is an unfaithful people please It is that
sea un infiel gente por favor Es que
this is from the Clan del cocu And that is not
este es de la del Clan del cocu Y eso no
the people are looking for the capture to be false
la gente está buscando que sea falsa la
or whatever eh Let's see if they can you
captura o sea eh A ver sí te pueden
never have to trust anything that is
nunca te tienes que fiar de nada de lo
on the internet that is clear and yes
que hay en internet eso está claro y lo
prove it simo now but man that a
y demostrad simo ya pero hombre que una
Random person who has never dedicated himself
persona Random que nunca se ha dedicado
to anything on YouTube appears or from YouTube
a nada de YouTube aparezca o de YouTube
I mean because maybe someone who rubs shoulders
me refiero porque a lo mejor alguien que
has Editors has people who  he
se codea tiene Editores tiene gente que
does things well, I know a thousand
te hace bien las cosas yo que sé mil
things, no, but it's quite credible, he has
cosas no pero es bastante creíble se ha
gone into the profile to pass the
metido en el perfil ha pasar las
stories at the moment he has updated he has
historias de momento ha actualizado ha
done it like this I mean it would have to be well edited it
hecho así O sea tendría que estar bien
would have to be well educ Uy very
editado tendría que estar bien educ Uy
well edited and you at the same time record
bien bien editado y tú a la vez grabar
the video swiping your finger on your phone
el vídeo pasando el dedo por tu móvil
to make those movements I
para hacer esos movimientos O
mean the truth is that
sea la verdad es que
other captures also came to light
también salieron a la luz otras capturas
where duky reacts to stories to a
donde duky reacciona historias a una
girl and they send photos the
chica y se mandan fotos no se sabe el
context of the
contexto de las
photos is unknown let's see
fotos a ver
you have something for
vos tenés algo para
me
mí
baby tonight I'm going to publish the
bebé hoy a la noche voy a publicar los
audios
audios
people are looking for them to be edited
la gente buscando que sean editados
of course go to sleep
claro a dormir
everyone That's it we have nothing more
todos Ya está no tenemos más nada
Javi I sent a thread in case you want to see it
Javi mandé un hilo por si lo quieres
let's see this
ver a ver vamos a ver este
go on cheating on this
anda que ponerle los cuernos a esta
girl
chavala
man let's see no matter what
tío a ver nunca sabes no
Hey well this account is the same one that
que Oye pues esta cuenta es la misma que
is funando al
está funando al
czu but very viral The funa of cocu eh
czu pero muy viral La funa de cocu eh
again
otra vez
Eh This is the same he has been
Eh Esto es lo mismo el ha sido
eliminated among the oddities of the chat
eliminado entre las rarezas del chat
there were
habían letras de
superimposed letters or for example some
superpuestas o por ejemplo algunas
parts of the chat were
partes del chat estaban
blurred letters
borrosas letras
superimposed the worst edition in
superpuestas la peor edición de la
history for this reason here
historia por esto de aquí
also bad dates
fechas también
November 12 but it doesn't say 2023 because
noviembre pero no dice 2023 porque aún
a year hasn't passed yet
no ha pasado un año
Ah here I would have to put 2023
Ah que aquí tendría que poner 2023
when a
cuando pasa un
year has passed, meaning this account is fake I
año o sea esta cuenta es de fakes
mean people contact this
O sea la gente contacta esta
account but this is a
cuenta pero esta es una cuenta
parody account an it
parodia an
is a parody account
es una cuenta parodia
dude when you see the coscu thing be
tío cuando veas lo de coscu tenga
careful because there appears a finger
cuidado ya que por ahí aparece un dedo
without a nail a fingerless finger 21 you know
sin uña un sin heso el dedo 21 ya sabes
what I mean XD I
a lo que me refiero XD
mean let's see luare what is a fake in the
O sea a ver luare qué es un fake al
end
final
Dale
Dale
no four
no cuatro
no Where to the Show Ho I go do you want to go
no A dónde al Show Ho yo voy quieres ir
no I mean I don't know
no O sea no sé
me me
me me
mime summary it didn't surprise us but stop
mir resumen no nos sorprendió pero para
because your objective was your objective but
porque tu objetivo era tu objetivo pero
if it goes up But I tell you well that yes I do That it
si suba Pero te digo bueno que s yo s
goes up
Que suba
but that
pero que
taste decle that way we see how they solve the
gust decle que así vemos cómo resuelven
per Ah well I wanted you to tell me a
per Ah buenoo quería que me cuentes un
little bit to make a little bit of you can
poquito para hacerle un poco de se puede
say how many topics I love I don't know
decir cuántos temas me encanta no
very well I thought you were going to p have
s muy bien Pensé que me ibas a p haber
asked me that always says that  how am I going to
preguntado eso siempre dice eso cómo voy
say seven are not cu but when he
a decir siete no son cu pero cuando lo
starts it when he wants Sorry sorry I
arranca cuando quiere Perdón perdón Yo
started wrong s songs together but no we don't
empecé mal s canciones juntos pero no no
plan any
planeamos ningún
kind what the
tipo qué
[ __ ] but let's see this could be Vero I
[__] pero a ver esto pueden ser a Vero
know it's not
sé no me es
enough for me I saw more
suficiente a gemita le vi más
flirting with Gemita then fake
coqueteo entonces fake
luar What conclusion can we
luar A qué conclusión podemos
reach, would it be fake or what Or would it be
llegar sería fake o qué O sería
real but of course that capture where she steps on
real pero claro esa captura que que pisa
the hedge is poorly edited something else has come out is
el seto está mal editada ha salido algo
real is true is
verdad es
fake we have to see if Duky is still with
fake hay que ver si duky se sigue con
Gemita let's
gemita
see what I think It looks like
a ver yo lo que creo Es que tiene pinta
fake no I mean there's a dance around there of
de fake no O sea hay un baile por ahí de
dates there's
fechas hay
one there's a capture that steps on the
un hay una captura que pisa la
other the one in the video I find it complicated that it
otra la del vídeo lo veo complicado que
's
sea
fake the one in the video I find it very complicated
fake la del vídeo lo veo muy complicado
that it's a fake it would have to be made
que sea un fake tendría que estar hecho
of the [ __ ] host So I think that
de la [__] [__] Entonces yo creo que
within all those captures that there will
dentro de todas esas capturas que hay
be some that are fake and others that are
habrá alg que sean fake y otras que sean
real to me the profile of the boy
reales a mí el perfil del del muchacho a
gives me a feeling and
mí me da sensación y
vibes Haha more fake than democracy in
vibras Jaja más falso que democracia en
cora like dat to Duki just released his
cora como dat to duki acaba de sacar su
Most anticipated album and it was obvious that
álbum Más esperado y era evidente que
one was going to come out Look for fame trying to
iba a salir una Busca famas tratando de
funar hold on  your
funar aguante el tu
cup let's see but you are a big fan So
copa a ver pero tú eres muy fan Entonces
from what I
por lo que
see I think something more realistic would be to
veo yo creo que algo más realista sería
think says luare I don't think so I think it's
pensar dice luare no creo yo creo que es
fake but believable let's see clear I think it's not
fake pero creíble a ver claro yo creo
something too far-fetched that it
que no es algo muy descabellado que no
wouldn't be crazy To find out that du
sería una locura Que enterarnos que du
hici was something like that but those screenshots in
hici era algo así pero esas capturas en
particular well no they don't have much they don't have
concreto pues no no tien mucha no tien
much credibility and then this has
mucha credibilidad y luego esto ha
caused this I don't know if I'll put it in
provocado que esto no sé si Lo pondré en
another separate tro But this has caused
otro tro aparte Pero esto ha provocado
the fun ducky or the attempt of Fun ducky
la fun ducky o el intento de Fun ducky
the funa
la funa
duki but I mean this has caused the
duki pero o sea esto lo ha provocado la
funa to ducky luare the fact that there are
funa a ducky luare el hecho de que haya
rumors that ducky had cheated on him
rumores de que ducky le hubiese puesto
or rather this comes from there not because as
o sea esto viene por ahí no porque como
they start to take out that ducky is unfaithful
empiezan a sacar que ducky es infiel
then they start to funar the cocu too I don't
pues empiezan a funar al cocu también no
understand that maybe Emilia's fans
entiendo que a lo mejor los fan de
violin alert Martn Prez and
Emilia alerta de violín Martín Pérez y
except thanks to the hidden files of the
salvo gracias a los archivos ocultos de
internet I found This video where the
internet encontré Este vídeo donde el
streamer koku confessed to his
streamer koku le confesaba a su víctima
underage victim How he raped and abused
menor de edad Como violaba y abusaba de
her while he was
ella mientras estaba
no no no you  you behaved like an
no no no te portaste como una hija
equal daughter in sex 10
de igual en el sexo 10
points
puntos
shortsighted your
miopa tu
clothes I tried to put the body so you would
ropa yo te intenté poner el corpo para
n't be naked and I put it on you But you
no est en pelotas y te lo puse Pero te
took it off by yourself
lo sacaste solo
no how bad [ __ ] video first time
no qu mal rollo [__] vídeo primera vez
I'm with a
que estoy con una
girl the files the hidden files
chica los archivos los archivos ocultos
of the internet give the
de internet da la
review How do you say it has like 2
review Cómo se dice tiene como 2
million views the
millones de visitas al
video
vídeo se
breaks down and The best part was when
descompone e La mejor parte fue cuando
you told me I want super lands I don't
decías quiero super tierras no me
remember I have what I don't remember no no it
acuerdo tengo qué no me acuerdo no no
disturbed the video eh [ __ ] But this
returbio el vídeo eh [__] Pero esto
lasts 41 minutes they uploaded
dura 41 minutos han subido aquí el
this live from cocu here this is the
directo este de cocu este es el vídeo
full video deleted by the pedophile but
completo borrado por el pederasta pero
recovered I mean this but this why was
recuperado o sea esto pero esto por qué
this why this luar this we know
esto por qué esto luar esto sabemos por
why this is these are Emilia's fans
qué es esto estos son los fans de Emilia
or why I mean this is something we already
o por qué o sea esto es algo que ya
knew he shared with his friend
sabíamos le compartió a su amigo
Jernimo momo accused of insinuating himself with a
Jerónimo momo acusado de insinuarse una
minor under 15 Romn a kiss this from Momo
menor de 15 Román un beso esto de Momo
What is accused of insinuating himself with a minor
Qué es acusado de insinuarse una menor
under 15 this photo next to the naked minor
de 15 esta foto junto a la menor desnuda
momo was in charge of spreading it
el momo se encargó de difundirla
no
no
cameo oh I can't I was saying to myself and I'm
cameo ay Es que no puedo me decía yo u
[ __ ] mad I had the dick Hey luar it doesn't
la [__] madreo tenía el [__] Oye luar no
look that old now this frame
se ve como muy antiguo ahora este marco
now that it's perfectly
ahora que está perfectamente
renovated now that it's perfectly
renovado ahora que está perfectamente
renovated
renovado
[ __ ] now it's seen in full HD
no [__] Ahora se ve Full HD
Now it's seen in full
Ahora se ve Full
HD And now you understand why the
HD Y ahora entendéis por qué las marcas
watermarks don't because when they're things that we
de agua no porque cuando son cosas que
found Only
encontramos Solo
us hard because the girl was hot good
nosotros duro porque la mina estaba
I had the hard dick and the m
buena buena yo tenía el [__] duro y el m
This was another episode that was found
Esto fue otro episodio que se encontró
luare that I said where the [ __ ] did you find
luare que dije dónde [__] has encontrado
this where the [ __ ] did you find this
esto dónde [__] has encontrado esto
this cl is gold eh I said oh I can't I
este cl es oro eh decía ay Es que no
was saying to myself and I'm [ __ ] mad I
puedo me decía y yo u la [__] madre yo
had the hard dick because the girl was hot
tenía el [__] duro porque la mina estaba
good I had the hard dick and the
buena buena yo tenía el [__] duro y el
fear of saying she's going to throw up all over my
miedo de decir me va a vomitar toda la
face we were lying in bed in
cara estábamos acostados en la cama en
a sleeping bag and the girl was there
una bolsa de dormir y la mina ahí
finishing but she said to me but but but
remataba pero me decía pero pero pero
Come on she said to me and I Come on it's all there
Dale me decía y yo Dale qu est ahí todo
like a thing lying there And I tried
como una cosa ahí tirada Y yo intentaba
but because I mean the girl tells me to take it
pero porque o sea la mina me dice que me
but she's asleep I mean no no not
la Agar pero está dormida o sea no no no
active and like she stays like that  half
activa y como que se queda así medio
asleep and fell
dormida y se quedaba
asleep says Lu they accused duki of being
dormida dice Lu acusaron a duki de
unfaithful and then her fans accused
infiel y luego sus fans la acusaron a
her of being unfaithful with
ella de infiel con
czu and they accused kku on the rebound or so this
czu y funaron a kku de rebote o sea esto
comes from ducky's funa eh let's see I'm going
viene por la funa de ducky eh a ver voy
to remove the screen but not for nothing
a quitar la pantalla pero no por nada
but because now the
sino porque ahora viene la
dick comes no
[__] no
what the
qué
[ __ ] How
[__] Cómo
Ah it was by accident because now the
Ah que fue sin querer porque ahora los
chat comments he looks at the screen
comentarios del chat él mira la pantalla
cuts the
corta el
live and the comments are cocu
directo y están los comentarios cocu
cocu they can suspend you I'm crying
cocu te pueden suspender estoy llorando
with laughter I don't know if I'm on Twitch or char
de risa no sé si estoy en Twitch o char
rulet now he
rulet ahora se dio
realized but this What is it he's not
cuenta pero esto Qué es no está
putting his dick in
metiéndole la [__] en la boca a
someone's mouth let's see I have my doubt that this
alguien a ver tengo mi duda de que esto
was by accident or that he did it on
sea sin querer o que lo hiciera
purpose and then he went crazy but
queriendo y luego se hiciera loco pero
why are you [ __ ] with
por qué te pones a [__] con los
these headphones on eh I mean
auriculares estos así puesto eh o sea
with these headphones and with the spotlight
con los auriculares estos y con el foco
on with the lights on in the
encendido con las luces encendidas del
room and in front of the camera it doesn't make
cuarto y delante de la cámara es que no
sense
tiene sentido
but he's alone it's
pero está solo
not that he's alone the moans I think it's
no es que está solo los gemidos creo que
him seeing something no
es él viendo algo no
anyway well he has more than 50,000 in the
en fin pues tiene más de 50.000 el el
thread eh more  of 50 let's see how much it has
hilo eh más de 50 a ver cuánto tiene
exactly
exactamente
see 22000
ver 22000
likes 3 million
likes 3 millones de
visits guys
visita chicos
I've done my part here for today I'm going
yo por hoy he cumplido por aquí me
to sleep and tomorrow will be another day I
voy a dormir y mañana será otro día que
want to get up tomorrow not too late
me quiero levantar mañana no muy tarde
to record another great video on the
para grabar otro pedazo de vídeo en el
main channel Tomorrow we are
canal principal Mañana estamos
preparing another great video on the
preparando otro pedazo de vídeo en el
main channel eh I don't know what time it will be it will be
canal principal eh que no sé a qué hora
at night I
estará estará por la noche me
imagine So stay tuned okay And
imagino Así que estaros pendient vale Y
above all go and give it that last
sobre todo iros a meterle el último
push I want to feel your body next to
empujón quiero sentir tu cuerpo juno al
mine it's
mío
not coscu anymore it's
ya no es coscu ahora es
cascu
cascu
go give that last little push to the
iros a meterle el último empujoncito al
video of the Main Channel from last night that
vídeo del Canal principal de anoche que
is about to reach 100,000 okay
está a nada de llegar a las 100.000 vale
it's missing 10,000 views go and
le faltan 10.000 visi tilla iros y le
give it that last push seven
metéis el último el último empujon sete
okay guys I'm going to sleep eh I
vale chicos yo me voy a dormir eh os
love you so much Thank you so much
quiero muchísimo Muchísimas gracias por
for being here I send you a
por haber estado por aquí os mando un
big kiss
beso muy fuerte
and tomorrow more and better
y mañana más y mejor
a kiss handsome
un beso guapos